Timothy Wangwe

Nairobi, Kenya



linkedin.com/in/timothy-wangwe



wangwetymothy@gmail.com



0706659609

Summary

As a kid, I dreamt of being Iron Man. It's been a little over a decade now and I'm currently pursuing a Bachelor's in Information Technology.

I have a passion for Data Science and Machine Learning. I think it's beautiful how we make our computers smarter by day and the amazing results it yields.

I believe in Integrity, Competence and humanity both as a Professional Art and a lifestyle.

Experience



Moringa School

Apr 2020 - Present (3 months +)

My main duty is to generate new leads among the campus population by using the following tactics:

- Identify and actively introduce Moringa School to campus groups/leaders.
- Increase campus penetration via on-campus tabling, email distribution and social media promotion.
- Developing your own creative ideas to assist in campus outreach efforts.
- Identifying the types of events most likely to engage students' imaginations and interests, and strategies to encourage attendance.

My other responsibilities are:

- Liaising with Moringa School and creating events within the school on behalf of Moringa School
- Create content and buzz for a new product launch

Mathematics - Physics Tutor

Kibunde High School

Jan 2019 - Apr 2019 (4 months)

My responsibilities were anchored in the following areas:

- Teach Physics to Forms 1 and 2
- Teach Mathematics to Forms 1 and 3
- Lead the Revision Programme for the Candidate Class

Education



Zetech University

Bachelor's degree, Information Technology 2019 - 2022

Licenses & Certifications

Cloud Intro - IBM

Data Science & Analytics Intro - IBM

Martificial Intelligence Intro - IBM

Honors & Awards

International President's Award for Distinguished Leo Presidents (2019-2020) - Lions Club International

Nov 2019

A multiple district council of governors or single district (that is not part of a multiple districts) may nominate one high achieving Leo each year for this medallion and certificate award.

Skills

Machine Learning Algorithms • Data Analysis • Django • Web Development • Analytics • Analytical Skills • Programming • Python (Programming Language) • Leadership • Team Management